(Sheldon:)I can't do this. I'm going to faint.
All right, drink this. It'll relax you.
(Sheldon:)-Alcohol? I don't drink alcohol.
-Fine, faint.
(Sheldon:)I don't feel different.
This alcohol's defective.
(Penny:)Here. See if this one works.
(Leonard(still talking):)First of all,
the projects were totally different.
(Leonard(still talking):)I was showing that classical music
nurtures lima beans...
(Leonard(still talking):)...and makes them grow.
But my mother didn't hear me.
If you look at the relationship
between nurturing and growth...
(Leonard(still talking):)...I'd like to point out that my brother
is 8 inches taller than me.
SHELDON:
I'm ready!
(Sheldon:)Right.
(Leonard:)Ladies and gentlemen,
our guest of honor...
(Leonard:)...Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
[APPLAUSE]
Thanks, shorty. I'll take it from here.
(Sheldon:)All right,
you people ready to have some fun?
You have an understanding
of differential calculus...